Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures and Audiorecordings Documenting Football
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Football game films, 1960-1962; Accession 2006-A-156
  - Harvard, 1962; 4 (Box 127–130)
  - Season highlights, 1962; 1 (Box 131)
    Narrated by Jordan Olivar.
  - JV vs. Bridgeport, 1962; 2 (Box 132–133)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1962; 2 (Box 134–135)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1962; 3 (Box 136–138)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1962; 2 (Box 139–140)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1962; 2 (Box 141–142)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1962; 2 (Box 143–144)
- Football game films, 1963-1964; Accession 2006-A-184
  - UConn, 1963; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - Brown, 1963; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Columbia, 1963; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Cornell, 1963; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Dartmouth, 1963; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Penn, 1963; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Princeton, 1963; 4 (Box 25–28)
  - Harvard, 1963; 4 (Box 29–32)
    - Use copy for boxes 29-32, 1 (Box 29U)
  - Boston University, 1963; 4 (Box 33–36)
  - Season highlights, 1963; 1 (Box 37)
  - JV vs. Brown, 1963; 4 (Box 38–41)
  - JV vs. Bridgeport, 1963; 4 (Box 42–44)
  - JV vs. Dartmouth, 1963; 4 (Box 45–48)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1963; 4 (Box 49–52)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1963; 3 (Box 53–55)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1963; 3 (Box 56–58)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1963; 4 (Box 59–62)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1963; 4 (Box 63–66)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1963; 2 (Box 67–68)
  - JV vs. Army, 1963; 4 (Box 69–72)
  - Scrimmages
    - 1963 Sep 11, 3 (Box 73–75)
    - 1963 Sep 17, 1 (Box 76)
    - 1963 Sep 19, 1 (Box 77)
  - Trinity, 1963; 4 (Box 78–81)
  - UConn, 1964 September 26; 4 (Box 82–85)
  - Lehigh
    - Wide-sequential, 1964; 4 (Box 86–89)
    - Sequential, 1964; 4 (Box 90–93)
  - Brown
    - Sequential, 1964; 4 (Box 94–97)
    - Wide, 1964; 4 (Box 98–101)
  - Columbia, 1964; 4 (Box 102–105)
  - Cornell, 1964; 4 (Box 106–109)
  - Dartmouth, 1964; 4 (Box 110–113)
  - Penn, 1964; 4 (Box 114–117)
    - Use copy for boxes 114-117, 1 (Box 114U)
  - Princeton, 1964; 4 (Box 118, Box 120–121)
    - Use copy for boxes 118, 120-121, 1 (Box 118U)
    - Color, 1964; 2 (Box 122–123)
    - Highlights, 1964; 1 (Box 124)
  - Harvard, 1964; 4 (Box 125–128)
    - Color, 1964; 3 (Box 129–131)
  - Boston University, 1964; 5 (Box 132–136)
  - Trinity, 1964; 4 (Box 137–140)
  - Season Highlights (narrated by Yale Head Coach John Pont), 1964; 1 (Box 141)
  - JV vs. Princeton, 1964; 4 (Box 142–145)
  - JV vs. Dartmouth, 1964; 4 (Box 146–149)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1964; 4 (Box 150–153)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1964; 3 (Box 154–156)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1964; 4 (Box 157–160)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1964; 4 (Box 161–164)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1964; 3 (Box 165–167)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1964; 4 (Box 168–171)
  - Scrimmages
    - First squad, 1964 September 3; 1 (Box 172)
    - Second squad, 1964 September 8; 4 (Box 173–176)
    - Third squad, 1964 September 8; 1 (Box 177)
    - Fourth squad, 1964 September 9; 4 (Box 178–181)
- Football game audiorecordings, 1998-2000; Accession 2006-A-251
  - Colgate, 1998 October 3; 2 (Box 1–2)
  - Holy Cross, 1998 October 10; 2 (Box 3–4)
  - Columbia, 1998 October 24; 2 (Box 5–6)
  - Penn, 1998 October 31; 2 (Box 7–8)
    - Use copy for boxes 7-8 (part 1), 1 (Box 7UA)
    - Use copy for boxes 7-8 (part 2), 1 (Box 7UB)
    - Use copy for boxes 7-8 (part 3), 1 (Box 8UA)
    - Use copy for boxes 7-8 (part 4), 1 (Box 8UB)
  - Cornell, 1998 November 7; 2 (Box 9–10)
  - Princeton, 1998 November 14; 2 (Box 11–12)
  - Harvard, 1998 November 21; 1 (Box 13)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 13U)
  - Harvard, 1998; 1 (Box 14)
  - Brown, 1999 September 18; 2 (Box 15–16)
    - Use copy, 2 (Box 15U–16U)
  - Holy Cross, 1999 October 9; 3 (Box 17–19)
  - Dartmouth, 1999 October 16; 1 (Box 20)
  - Columbia, 1999 October 23; 3 (Box 21–23)
  - Penn (sides 1-2, 5-6; no side 3-4), 1999 October 30; 3 (Box 24–25)
    - Use copy for boxes 24-25 (part 1), 1 (Box 24U)
    - Use copy for boxes 24-25 (part 2), 1 (Box 25UA)
    - Use copy for boxes 24-25 (part 3), 1 (Box 25UB)
  - Cornell, 1999 November 6; 2 (Box 27–28)
  - Princeton, 1999 November 13; 3 (Box 29–31)
  - Dayton, 2000 September 16; 2 (Box 32–33)
  - Cornell, 2000 September 23; 2 (Box 34–35)
  - Holy Cross, 2000; 1 (Box 36)
  - Dartmouth, undated; 1 (Box 37)
  - Holy Cross, undated; 1 (Box 38)
  - Conversation about Yale-Harvard football, undated; 1 (Box 39)
- Football game films, 1965-1966; Accession 2007-A-003
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 3–4)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 9–10)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 11–12)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1965; 1 (Box 17)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 18–19)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 20–23)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 24–25)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 26–27)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 28–31)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 32–33)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 34–35)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 36–39)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 40–41)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 42–43)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 44–47)
      - Use copy for boxes 44-47, 1 (Box 44U)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 48–49)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 50–51)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 52–55)
      - Use copy for boxes 52-55, 1 (Box 52U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 56–57)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 58–59)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 60–63)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1965; 2 (Box 64–65)
    - Offense, 1965; 2 (Box 66–67)
    - Sequential, 1965; 4 (Box 68–71)
  - Trinity, 1965; 4 (Box 72–75)
  - Season Highlights, 1965; 1 (Box 76)
    Narrated by Yale Head Coach Carmen Cozza.
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 76U)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1965; 4 (Box 77–80)
  - JV vs. Dartmouth, 1965; 4 (Box 81–84)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1965; 3 (Box 85–87)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1965; 4 (Box 88–91)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1965; 4 (Box 92–95)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1965; 4 (Box 96–99)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1965; 1 (Box 100)
  - Freshmen vs. SCSU, 1965; 1 (Box 101)
  - Scrimmage vs. BU, 1965; 4 (Box 102–105)
  - UConn, 1966; 4 (Box 106–109)
  - Rutgers, 1966; 4 (Box 110–113)
  - Brown, 1966; 4 (Box 114–117)
  - Columbia, 1966; 4 (Box 118–121)
  - Cornell, 1966; 4 (Box 122–125)
  - Dartmouth, 1966; 4 (Box 126–129)
  - Penn, 1966; 4 (Box 130–133)
    - Use copy for boxes 130-133, 1 (Box 130U)
  - Princeton, 1966; 4 (Box 134–137)
    - Use copy for boxes 134-137, 1 (Box 134U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1966; 2 (Box 138–139)
  - Harvard
    - Sequential, 1966; 4 (Box 140–143)
      - Use copy for boxes 140-143, 1 (Box 140U)
    - Offense, 1966; 2 (Box 144–145)
  - Season Highlights, 1966; 1 (Box 146)
    Narrated by Head Coach Carm Cozza.
  - Passing, 1966; 1 (Box 147)
  - Punt Return, 1966; 1 (Box 148)
  - 70 Games, 1966; 2 (Box 149–150)
  - 40 Games, 1966; 2 (Box 151–152)
  - 28-528 and run pass, 1966; 1 (Box 153)
  - 28-526, 1966; 1 (Box 154)
  - Kick off, 1966; 1 (Box 155)
  - Punt, 1966; 1 (Box 156)
  - Field Goal and P.A.T., 1966; 1 (Box 157)
  - JV vs. Trinity, 1966; 2 (Box 158–159)
  - JV vs. Dartmouth, 1966; 2 (Box 160–161)
  - JV vs. Columbia, 1966; 3 (Box 162–164)
  - JV vs. Princeton, 1966; 3 (Box 165–167)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1966; 4 (Box 168–171)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1966; 4 (Box 172–175)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1966; 4 (Box 176–179)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1966; 2 (Box 180–181)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1966; 3 (Box 182–184)
  - Scrimmage vs. Bucknell, 1966; 4 (Box 185–188)
  - Sprint, 1966; 1 (Box 189)
- Football game films, 1967-1968; Accession 2007-A-030
  - Holy Cross
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 3–4)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 9–10)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 11–12)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 17–18)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 19–20)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Columbia
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 25–26)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 27–30)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 31–32)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 33–34)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 35–38)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1967 November 4; 2 (Box 39–40)
    - Offense, 1967 November 4; 2 (Box 41–42)
    - Sequential [b/w], 1967 November 4; 4 (Box 43–46)
      - Use copy for boxes 43-46, 1 (Box 43U)
    - Sequential [color], 1967 November 4; 2 (Box 47–48)
      - Use copy for boxes 47-48, 1 (Box 47U)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 49–50)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 51–52)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 53–56)
      - Use copy for boxes 53-56, 1 (Box 53U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 57–58)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 59–60)
    - Sequential (includes JV), 1967; 6 (Box 61–66)
    - Highlights, 1967; 1 (Box 67)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1967; 2 (Box 68–69)
    - Offense, 1967; 2 (Box 70–71)
    - Sequential, 1967; 4 (Box 72–75)
    - Highlights, 1967; 1 (Box 76)
  - Trinity, 1967; 4 (Box 77–80)
  - Season Highlights, 1967; 1 (Box 81)
  - JV vs. West Point, 1967; 2 (Box 82–83)
  - JV vs. Harvard, 1967; 2 (Box 84–85)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1967; 2 (Box 86–87)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1967; 4 (Box 88–91)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1967; 3 (Box 92–94)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1967; 4 (Box 95–98)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1967; 3 (Box 99–101)
  - Laurel Crest, 1967; 2 (Box 102–103)
  - Freshmen vs. Varsity, 1967; 2 (Box 104–105)
  - Columbia Defense, 1967; film reel (16mm) (Box 106)
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 107–108)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 109–110)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 111–114)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 115–116)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 117–118)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 119–122)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 123–124)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 125–126)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 127–130)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 131–132)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 133–134)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 135–138)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 139–140)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 141–142)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 143–146)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 147–148)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 149–150)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 151–154)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 155–156)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 157–158)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 159–162)
      - Use copy for boxes 159-162, 1 (Box 159U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1968; 2 (Box 163–164)
    - Offense, 1968; 2 (Box 165–166)
    - Sequential, 1968; 4 (Box 167–170)
  - Princeton (under scoreboard), 1968; 2 (Box 171–172)
  - Season highlights, 1968; 1 (Box 173)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 173U1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 173U2)
  - Freshmen vs. Fairfield?, 1968; 4 (Box 174–177)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1968; 4 (Box 178–181)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1968; 4 (Box 182–185)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1968; 4 (Box 186–189)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1968; 3 (Box 190–192)
- Football game films, 1968-1970; Accession 2007-A-033
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Offense, 1969; 2 (Box 3–4)
    - Sequential, 1969; 4 (Box 5–8)
      - Use copy for boxes 5-8, 1 (Box 5U)
    - Sequential (color), 1969; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 13–14)
    - Offense, 1969; 3 (Box 15–17)
    - Sequential (includes JV), 1969; 5 (Box 18–22)
    - Sequential (color), 1969; 3 (Box 23–25)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 26–27)
    - Offense, 1969; 2 (Box 28–29)
    - Sequential (includes JV), 1969; 5 (Box 30–34)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 35–36)
    - Offense, 1969; 2 (Box 37–38)
    - Sequential (includes JV), 1969; 5 (Box 39–43)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 44–45)
    - Offense, 1969; 2 (Box 46–47)
    - Sequential (includes JV), 1969; 5 (Box 48–52)
  - Penn
    - Offense, 1969; film reel (16mm) (Box 53)
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 54–55)
    - Sequential, 1969; 4 (Box 56–59)
      - Use copy for boxes 56-59, 1 (Box 56U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 60–61)
    - Offense, 1969; 2 (Box 62–63)
    - Sequential, 1969; 4 (Box 64–67)
    - Sequential?, 1969; 1 (Box 92)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 68–69)
    - Sequential, 1969; 2 (Box 70–71)
      - Use copy for boxes 70-71, 1 (Box 70U)
  - Season highlights, 1969; 1 (Box 72)
  - SCSU
    - Defense, 1969; 2 (Box 73–74)
    - Offense, 1969; 2 (Box 75–76)
  - Trinity JV scrimmage, 1969; 3 (Box 77–79)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1969; 4 (Box 80–83)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1969; 4 (Box 84–87)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1969; 4 (Box 88–91)
  - Harvard, 1969; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 97–98)
    - Offense, 1970; 2 (Box 99–100)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 105–106)
    - Offense, 1970; 2 (Box 107–108)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 109–112)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 113–114)
    - Offense, 1970; 2 (Box 115–116)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 117–120)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 121–122)
    - Offense, 1970; 2 (Box 123–124)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 125–128)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 129–130)
    - Offense, 1970; 2 (Box 131–132)
  - Dartmouth defense, 1970; 1 (Box 133)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 134–135)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 136–139)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 140–141)
    - Offense, 1970; 2 (Box 142–143)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 144–147)
    - Princeton - unidentified, 1968?; 1 (Box 171)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1970; 2 (Box 148–149)
    - Sequential, 1970; 4 (Box 150–153)
  - Season highlights, 1970; 1 (Box 154)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 154U)
  - JV vs. Dartmouth, 1970; 4 (Box 155–158)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1970; 4 (Box 159–162)
  - Freshmen vs. STM, 1970; 4 (Box 163–166)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1970; 4 (Box 167–170)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1968?; 3 (Box 172–174)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1970; 4 (Box 175–178)
  - Freshmen vs. UConn Scrimmage, 1970; 3 (Box 179–181)
- Football game films, 1971-1972; Accession 2007-A-046
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 3–4)
    - Sequential, 1971; 4 (Box 5–8)
      - Duplicating master for film reels 5-8, 7
      - Use copy for film reels 5-8, 1 (Box 5U)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 9–10)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 11–12)
    - Sequential, 1971; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 17–18)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 19–20)
    - Sequential, 1971; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 25–26)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 27–28)
    - Sequential, 1971; 4 (Box 29–32)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 33–34)
      - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
        General note
        Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
      - Use copy for boxes 33-34, 1 (Box 33U)
    - Defense (duplicate copy), 1971; 2 (Box 37–38)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 35–36)
      - Duplicating master, computer files (DVD-Video)
      - Use copy for boxes 35-36, 1 (Box 33U)
    - Offense (duplicate copy), 1971; 2 (Box 39–40)
  - Dartmouth, 1971; 4 (Box 41–44)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 45–46)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 47–48)
    - Sequential, 1971; 4 (Box 49–52)
      - Use copy for boxes 49-52, 1 (Box 49U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 53–54)
    - Offense, 1971; 2 (Box 55–56)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1971; 2 (Box 57–58)
    - Sequential, 1971; 4 (Box 59–62)
  - Trinity, 1971; 4 (Box 63–66)
  - SCSU, 1971; 4 (Box 67–70)
  - Season Highlights, 1971; 1 (Box 71)
  - Curl back, 1971; 1 (Box 72)
  - 28, 1971; 1 (Box 73)
  - 48, 1971; 1 (Box 74)
  - 46, 1971; 2 (Box 75–76)
  - 80T, 1971; 1 (Box 77)
  - 84, 1971; 1 (Box 78)
  - 532 Boot, 1971; 1 (Box 79)
  - 546, 1971; 1 (Box 80)
  - 64, 1971; 1 (Box 81)
  - Delays, 1971; 1 (Box 82)
  - Sciss, 1971; 1 (Box 83)
  - Draw, 1971; 1 (Box 84)
  - 26-4, 1971; 1 (Box 85)
  - 564, 1971; 1 (Box 86)
  - Sprint, 1971; 1 (Box 87)
  - 86, 1971; 1 (Box 88)
  - TB, 1971; 1 (Box 89)
  - JV, 1971 October 8; 4 (Box 90–93)
  - Freshmen vs. Milford, 1971; 3 (Box 94–96)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1971; 4 (Box 97–100)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1971; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1971; 4 (Box 105–108)
  - Freshmen vs. St. T. Moore, 1971; 4 (Box 109–112)
  - Freshmen vs. UConn, 1971; 3 (Box 113–115)
  - Freshmen, 1971 September 18; 2 (Box 116–117)
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 118–119)
      - Use copy for boxes 118-119, 1 (Box 118U)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 120–121)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 122–125)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 126–127)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 128–129)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 130–133)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 134–135)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 136–137)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 138–141)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 142–143)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 144–145)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 146–149)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 150–151)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 152–153)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 154–155, Box 191–192)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 156–157)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 158–159)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 160–163)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 164–165)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 166–167)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 168–171)
      - Use copy for boxes 168-171, 1 (Box 168U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 172–173)
    - Offense, 1972; 2 (Box 174–175)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 176–179)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1972; 2 (Box 180–181)
    - Offense, 1972; 1 (Box 182)
    - Sequential, 1972; 4 (Box 183–186)
  - Season highlights, 1972; 1 (Box 187)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1972; 2 (Box 188–189)
  - Play 28, 1972; 1 (Box 190)
- Football game films, 1973-1974; Accession 2007-A-075
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 3–4)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 5–6)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 7–8)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 13–14)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 15, Box 196)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 16–19)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 20–21)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 22–23)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 24–27)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 28–29)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 30–31)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 32–35)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 32U)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 36–37)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 38–39)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 40–43)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 44–45)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 46–47)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 48–51)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 52–53)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 149–150)
    - Sequential, 1973; 4 (Box 54–57)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1973; 2 (Box 58–59)
    - Offense, 1973; 2 (Box 60–61)
  - Season highlights, 1973; film reel (16mm) (Box 62)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 62U)
  - JV, 1973 October 8; 4 (Box 63–66)
  - Freshmen vs. UConn, 1973; 2 (Box 67–68)
  - Freshmen vs. Army, 1973; 4 (Box 69–72)
  - Freshmen vs. Milford, 1973; 2 (Box 73–74)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1973; 3 (Box 75–77)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1973; 3 (Box 78–80)
  - Freshmen, 1973 September 8; 2 (Box 81–82)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1973; 4 (Box 83–86)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1973; 4 (Box 87–90)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1973; 3 (Box 91–92, Box 197)
  - Freshmen vs. St. Thomas More, 1973; 2 (Box 93–94)
  - Scrimmage vs. Dartmouth, 1973; 3 (Box 95–97)
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 98–99)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 100–101)
    - Sequential, 1974; 4 (Box 102–105)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 106–107)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 108–109)
    - Sequential, 1974; 4 (Box 110–113)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 114–115)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 116–117)
    - Sequential, 1974; 3 (Box 118–120)
  - Columbia
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 121–122)
    - Sequential, 1974; 4 (Box 123–125, Box 198)
      - Use copy for boxes 123-125 and 198, 1 (Box 123U)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 126–127)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 128–129)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 130–131)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 132–133)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 134–135)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 136–137)
    - Sequential, 1974; 4 (Box 138–140, Box 199)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 141–142)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 143–144)
    - Sequential, 1974; 4 (Box 145–148)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1974; 2 (Box 151–152)
    - Offense, 1974; 2 (Box 153–154)
  - Season highlights, 1974; 1 (Box 155)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 155U)
  - Rutgers, 1974; 4 (Box 156–159)
  - 64, 1974; 2 (Box 160–161)
  - Draw 18-80-24-4+RA; Run-32, 1974; 1 (Box 162)
  - Fly Dump Hook Post, 1974; 1 (Box 163)
  - 44, 1974; 1 (Box 164)
  - 48, 1974; 1 (Box 165)
  - 38, 1974; 1 (Box 166)
  - Hook-Road-Curl-Deep-"S", 1974; 1 (Box 167)
  - Special Pass-Delay-Rollaway-Drag-Screen Flash, 1974; 1 (Box 168)
  - 28, 1974; 2 (Box 169–170)
  - Punts and extra points, 1974; 1 (Box 171)
  - Kickoff returns, 1974; 1 (Box 172)
  - Freshmen vs. JV
    - Defense, 1974 September 20; 1 (Box 173)
    - Offense, 1974 September 20; 1 (Box 174)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1974; 3 (Box 175–177)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1974; 4 (Box 178–181)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1974; 4 (Box 182–185)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1974; 4 (Box 186–189)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1974; 3 (Box 190–192)
  - Freshmen scrimmage vs. UConn, 1974; 3 (Box 193–195)
- Football game films, 1975-1976; Accession 2007-A-086
  - UConn
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 3–4)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Colgate
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 9–10)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 11–12)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Brown
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 17–18)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 19–20)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Columbia
    - Defense, 1975; 1 (Box 25)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 26–27)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 28–31)
    - Sequential (color), 1975; 4 (Box 32–35)
  - Cornell
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 36–37)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 38–39)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 40–43)
    - Sequential (color), 1975; 4 (Box 44–47)
  - Dartmouth
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 48–49)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 50–53)
    - Sequential (color), 1975; 4 (Box 54–57)
  - Penn
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 58–59)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 60–61)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 62–65)
    - Sequential (color), 1975; 4 (Box 66–69)
      - Use copy for boxes 66-69, 1 (Box 66U)
  - Princeton
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 70–71)
    - Offense, 1975; 1 (Box 72)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 73–76)
    - Sequential (color), 1975; 4 (Box 77–80)
  - Harvard
    - Defense, 1975; 2 (Box 81–82)
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 83–84)
    - Sequential, 1975; 4 (Box 85–88)
    - Sequential (color), 1975; 4 (Box 89–92)
  - UMass
    - Offense, 1975; 2 (Box 93–94)
  - Season Highlights, 1975; 1 (Box 95)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 95U)
  - Punt, 1975; 1 (Box 96)
  - Kickoff Returns, 1975; 1 (Box 97)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1975; 3 (Box 98–100)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1975; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1975; 4 (Box 105–108)
  - Freshmen vs. St. Thomas More, 1975 September 26; 3 (Box 109–111)
    - Use copy for boxes 109-111, 1 (Box 109U)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1975; 4 (Box 112–115)
  - Freshmen vs. SCSU, 1975; 3 (Box 116–118)
  - Freshmen vs. Milford, 1975; 4 (Box 119–122)
  - Freshmen, 1975 September 25; 2 (Box 123–124)
  - Freshmen vs. Sophomores, 1975; 1 (Box 125)
  - Punts & Extra Points, 1975; 1 (Box 126)
  - Roll & Jet, 1975; 1 (Box 127)
  - 24 & 26, 1975; 1 (Box 128)
  - 44, 1975; 1 (Box 129)
  - 80, 1975; 1 (Box 130)
  - 28 I, 1975; 1 (Box 131)
  - 48, 1975; 1 (Box 132)
  - 28 II, 1975; 1 (Box 133)